# MohammadAli Attar Olyaei

Full Stack Web Developer



• Iran, Mashhad

### **Profile**

As a skilled full-stack developer, I excel in PHP and Laravel for server-side development and React.js for client-side implementation. With a track record of successful projects, I specialize in creating efficient web applications, optimizing performance, and ensuring seamless user experiences. Let's work together to turn your ideas into reality!

## **Education**

Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering,

Sajjad Industrial University 09/2018 - 06/2023 | Mashhad, Iran

### **Skills**

React.js • React Redux • React PWA

JavaScript • TypeScript • Tailwind

Bootstrap • Material UI • Chakra UI

¡Query • HTML & CSS • PHP • Laravel

MySQL • Rest Api • Git • Java • Katlin

Android • Adobe Illustrator

## **Professional Experience**

Full Stack Developer, KaraJet 03/2022 - 04/2023 | Mashhad, Iran

FrontEnd Developer, Respina24 03/2020 - 01/2022 | Mashhad, Iran

**Android Developer, OMP Finex** 05/2019 - 12/2019 | Mashhad, Iran

## **Projects**

#### My Portfolio

This is my personal website implemented using React.js, where you can view my resumes. One of the features of this website is the ability to customize the color scheme according to your preferences. Link 🗆

## **Aparat website**

This project is a complete implementation of the popular Aparat website, with Laravel on the server-side and React.js on the client-side. Link Γ2

## **GameHub website**

This website is implemented using React.js and UI-Chakra. It allows you to easily find your favorite games using the search and filter features. (Please turn on your VPN to view the site demo.) Link 🗷

## **Radio Javan website**

This project has been implemented using PHP, HTML, CSS, JS, and Bootstrap, creating a beautiful and functional website. Link 🛮

## **CinemaTicket website**

This project is a complete implementation of the Cinematicket website, developed using Laravel on the server-side and jQuery, JS, CSS, HTML, and Tailwind on the client-side.soon the demo will be available

#### **Android App Truth or Dare**

This project has been implemented using Java. Link 🗷

#### **Facebook website**

This project has been implemented using PHP, HTML, CSS, JS, and Bootstrap, creating a beautiful and functional website.